Guide to the Larry Goodell Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Larry Goodell papers
1954-2016
YCAL MSS 1095
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
18.25
(18 boxes)
The Larry Goodell Papers, which span from 1954 to 2016, contain correspondence, writings, business records, posters, audiovisual materials, electronic media, printed material, and other papers by or related to Larry Goodell and Duende Press. The papers contain writings of Larry Goodell as well as correspondence, poetry, and other writings from many poets with whom Goodell had personal relationships or business connections through Duende Press. The records of Duende Press document business dealings between 1968 and 2008, primarily in the form of writings submitted to the press from a variety of poets. Photographs and audiovisual materials,spanning 1968 to 2013, make up the smallest portion of the collection and primarily document poetry readings and performances by Goodell and other regional poets from the Southwestern United States.
Goodell, Larry, 1935-
Duende Press
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 15-16 (digital media): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Box 17 (audiocassette): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Granary Books, Inc. on the Ezra Pound Archive Fund, 2016.
Arrangement
Organized into six series: I. Correspondence and Writings, 1954-2016. II. Duende Press Records, 1964-2010. III. Berkeley and Vancouver Poetry Conference Papers, 1963-1965. IV. Flyers, 1978-2010. V. Personal Papers, 1968-2005. VI. Audiovisual Materials, 1986-2008.
Larry Goodell
Larry Goodell, a prolific poet and publisher, was born in Roswell, New Mexico in 1935. After studying at University of Southern California and the University of New Mexico, Goodell settled in Placitas, New Mexico and started Duende Press in 1964. Duende Press published not only Goodell's poetry, but also the works of other poets such as his former teacher Robert Creeley. Goodell actively participated in the poetry and performance communities of the Southwestern United States, hosting many readings and events from the mid-1960's onward. Goodell also maintained extensive personal and business correspondences with a variety of poets, authors and artists.
Scope and Contents
The Larry Goodell Papers, which span from 1954 to 2016, contain correspondence, writings, business records, posters, audiovisual materials, electronic media, printed material, and other papers by or related to Larry Goodell and Duende Press. The papers contain writings of Larry Goodell as well as correspondence, poetry, and other writings from many poets with whom Goodell had personal relationships or business connections through Duende Press. The records of Duende Press document business dealings between 1968 and 2008, primarily in the form of writings submitted to the press from a variety of poets. Photographs and audiovisual materials,spanning 1968 to 2013, make up the smallest portion of the collection and primarily document poetry readings and performances by Goodell and other regional poets from the Southwestern United States.
American poetry -- 20th Century; American poetry -- 21st century; Publishers and publishing -- New Mexico; Poetry -- Publishing -- New Mexico; Poetry -- Study and teaching -- New Mexico; Oral interpretation of poetry; Poets, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Poets, American -- 21st century -- Archives; Audiovisual materials; Born digital; Photographs; Poets -- United States -- 20th Century; Poets -- United States -- 21st century; Goodell, Larry, 1935-; Duende Press
- Correspondence, 1954-2016; Series I; 8.67; (8 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Primarily arranged alphabetically by correspondent's last name. Some unsorted correspondence is filed after the alphabetically arranged materials.
  Scope and Contents
  Contains correspondence, along with poetry, other writings, and ephemera that were included with the correspondence. The material documents personal and business relationships related to Larry Goodell and Duende Press. Poetry and other writings by Goodell can also be found in Series II, Duende Press records.
  - "A" General, 1964-1991 (Box 1)
  - Aaron, Richard, 1975 (Box 1)
    Contains correspondence and writings related to Am Here Books.
  - Abbot, Ward (Terry), 1969-1975 (Box 1)
  - Abel, David, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Abrams, Sam, 1965 (Box 1)
    Includes correspondence to and from Larry Goodell.
  - Alexander, Charles, 1983-1999; 2 folders (Box 1)
    Contains correspondence and writings related to Chax Press.
  - Alexander, D., 1964-1966 (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Floyce, 1971-2006 (Box 1)
  - Anania, Michael, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Anaya, Rudolfo A., undated (Box 1)
  - Alpert, Barry, 1972-1976 (Box 1)
  - Andre, Michael, 1975-1988 (Box 1)
  - Andrews, Bruce, undated (Box 1)
  - "B" General, 1966-1988 (Box 1)
  - B--submitted writings, 1980-2000 (Box 1)
  - Bakken, Dick, 1974-1991; (5 folders) (Box 1)
    Includes correspondence, clippings, and papers related to the Bisbee Poetry Festival.
  - Barba, Sharon Rose, 1992 (Box 1)
    Includes writings and correspondence.
  - Barton, Brett, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
    Includes correspondence and writings.
  - Bassara, Robert, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Bayes, Ronald, 1964-1970; (5 folders) (Box 1)
    Includes correspondence to and from Larry Goodell, writings, and cards.
  - Beltrametti, Franco, undated (Box 1)
  - Benedetti, David, 1972-1994 (Box 1)
  - Benedetti, Davis, undated (Box 1)
  - Bennahum, David A., 1986-1991 (Box 1)
  - Bennett, John, 1974 (Box 1)
    Includes correspondence and writings related to Vagabond Press.
  - Bennett, John M., 1979 (Box 1)
    Includes correspondence and writings related to Luna Bisonte Prods.
  - Benson, Steve, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Bergé, Carol, 1964-1984 (Box 1)
    Includes writings, as well as correspondence to and from Larry Goodell.
  - Bernhardt, Robert James, 1997-1998 (Box 1)
  - Bersenbrugge, Mei-Mei, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Bertholf, Robert, 1978-1998 (Box 1)
  - Blackburn, Paul, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Blaisdell, Gus, 1973-1999; (2 folders) (Box 1)
    Includes writings, as well as correspondence related to Living Batch Bookstore.
  - Blaser, Robin, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Blatt, Veryl, 1964 (Box 1)
  - Blazek, Doug, 1964-1965 (Box 1)
  - Bodner, Richard, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Bottone, Joe, circa 1969-1975; (3 folders) (Box 1)
  - Boudzuck, Bruce (Fred Merz), 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Brakhage, Stan, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Brandi, John, 1974-1988; (3 folders) (Box 1)
    Includes correspondence and postcards.
  - Brenner, Summer, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Brigham, Besmir, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Bright, Susan, circa 1984 (Box 1)
  - Bromige, David, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Brower, Gary, 1974-2006 (Box 2)
    Including correspondence and writings.
  - Brown, Rebecca, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Bryan, Jeff, 1988-2009; (2 folders) (Box 2)
    Including cards, as well as correspondence to and from Larry Goodell.
  - Buffington, Mel, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Burke, Clifford, 2001-2013; (2 folders) (Box 2)
    Includes correspondence related to Desert Rose Press.
  - Butterick, George, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Byrd, Bobby, 1974-1991; (3 folders) (Box 2)
    Includes correspondence to and from Larry Goodell, as well as writings.
  - "C" General, 1964-2009; (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - C--submitted writings, undated (Box 2)
  - Campbell, Everett, 1985-1989 (Box 2)
    Everett Campbell served as editor of Crow Call.
  - Cannon, Janet, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
    Janet Cannon served as an editor of Crow Call.
  - Caplan, Ronald, 1964-1970; (3 folders) (Box 2)
    Includes correspondence to and from Larry Goodell, cards, and writings.
  - Cassidy, Neal/Diane Sward, undated (Box 2)
  - Chapin, Hank, 1962-1974 (Box 2)
    Includes correspondence to and from Larry Goodell, as well as writings. Hank Chapin served as an editor for Blue Grass.
  - Chautauqua Programs, 1995-2000 (Box 2)
    Includes correspondence and papers related to the Chautauqua Programs sponsored by the New Mexico Endowment for the Humanities. During these programs, performers took on the persona a historical figure--Larry Goodell performed as Vachel Lindsay.
  - Church, Peggy Pond, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Chorlton, David and Roberta, 1984-1991 (Box 2)
  - Christensen, Carl, 1976-1981 (Box 2)
    Includes correspondence and writings related to Carl Christensen's life as Living Batch Bookstore manager, filmmaker, tile maker, Buddhist.
  - Christensen, Francis, 1955 (Box 2)
    Francis Christensen was Larry Goodell's linguistics teacher.
  - Christensen, Peter, 1981 (Box 2)
  - Circus Nation Network, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Clancy, Patrick, 1980-1983 (Box 2)
  - Clark, Laverne Harrell, 1988-1991 (Box 2)
  - Clark, Tom, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Coleman, Victor, undated (Box 2)
  - Colino, Peter, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Collom, Jack, 1965-1976; (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - Congdon, Kirby, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Connor, Lee, 1977-2015; (3 folders) (Box 2)
    Includes correspondence, ephemera, and a copy of Larry Goodell's "Dance Book".
  - Coolidge, Clark, undated (Box 2)
  - Cooney, Seamus, 1966-1969 (Box 2)
  - Corman, Cid, 1980 (Box 2)
  - Creeley, Robert, 1962-1967 (Box 2)
    Includes correspondence to and from Larry Goodell, as well as University of New Mexico course materials.
  - Creighton, Jane, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Crews, Judson, 1972-1986 (Box 2)
    Includes correspondence from Carol Berge
  - Crozier, Andrew, undated (Box 2)
  - "D" General, 1965-2007 (Box 2)
  - D--submitted writings, undated (Box 2)
  - D'alessandro, Robert and Sara, 1978-2004; (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Dawson, Fielding and Susan Maldovan, 1975-1998; (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Dietz, Chris, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Dodd, William, 1964-1966; (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Dorn, Ed, 1963-2001 (Box 3)
  - Dowden, George, 1964-1966 (Box 3)
  - Duerden, Richard, 1965-1966 (Box 3)
  - "E" General, 1965-2003 (Box 3)
  - Edelstein, J. M., 1964-1966 (Box 3)
  - Eigner, Larry, 1963-1974; (3 folders) (Box 3)
    Includes correspondence, postcards, and writings.
  - Ellingham, Lewis, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Elliston, Pancho, 1981-2011 (Box 3)
  - Enslin, Ted, 1964-1994; (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Eshleman, Clayton, 1966-1991 (Box 3)
  - Essary, Loris, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
  - "F" General, 1981-1992 (Box 3)
  - Finstein, Max, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Fisher, Thomas Michael, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Fles, John, undated (Box 3)
  - Fox, Hugh, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Fowler, Gene, 1981-1988; (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Franklyn, A. Frederic, 1963-1967; (3 folders) (Box 3)
  - Franks, David, 1967-2006; (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Frechette, Dan, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Fritz, David and Stefa, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Frumkin, Gene, 1976-2007 (Box 3)
    Includes writings by Larry Goodell and correspondence.
  - Frym, Gloria, 1976-2002 (Box 3)
  - Fuchs, Paul and Limpe, undated (Box 3)
  - "G" General, 1965-1990; (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Gaburo, Kenneth (Lingua Press), 1979 (Box 3)
  - Gallegos, Robert, undated (Box 3)
  - Garland, Peter, 1981 (Box 3)
  - George, Charley, 1989 (Box 3)
  - George, Barbara, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Gill, Lisa and Olivia Gatwood, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Gilb, Dagoberto, 1986-1990; (4 folders) (Box 3)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Glover, Al, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Goodell, Larry, 1956-2012; (4 folders) (Box 3)
  - Goodtimes, Art, 1991-2005; (3 folders) (Box 3)
    Includes correspondence and writings related to the Talking Gourds Poetry Club.
  - Grahn, Judy and Wendy Cadden, 1971-2007 (Box 3)
  - Gray, Darrell, undated (Box 3)
  - Greene, Jonathan, 1965-1990 (Box 3)
  - Gregorio, Rene and Marianne E. Sullivan, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Grossinger, Richard, undated (Box 3)
  - Grothus, Barbara (Albuquerque artist and activist), 1978 (Box 3)
  - Guralnick, Tom, 1985-1991 (Box 3)
  - "H" General, 1961-1993 (Box 4)
  - Hadley, Drummond and Diana, 1971-1979 (Box 4)
  - Hanlon, Chris, 1959-1965; (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Harris, Jim, 1981-1983 (Box 4)
  - Harris, Latif (William), 1965-2007; (4 folders) (Box 4)
  - Hartz, Jim, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Hejinian, Lyn, 1975; (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Hermann, Vivienne, 1988 (Box 4)
    Includes correspondence and a draft of "Confronting Holocausts".
  - Hiatt, Ben L., 1975 (Box 4)
  - Higgins, Dick, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Hirschman, Jack, undated; (2 folders) (Box 4)
    Includes a poem and letter to Latif Harris, as well as other assorted correspondence.
  - Hollo, Anselm, 1964-1990 (Box 4)
  - Holman, Bob, 1979-1981 (Box 4)
  - Hornick, Lita (Kulchur), 1965 (Box 4)
  - Howard, Cheryl (Albuquerque and El Paso), 1979 (Box 4)
  - Howden, Bill, undated (Box 4)
  - Huntress, Diana, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Inman, Will, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Irby, Ken, 1973-2010; (9 folders) (Box 4)
    Includes correspondence, writings, and an anthology developed between Goodell and Irby.
  - Isaacson, Jody, 1994 (Box 4)
  - "J" General, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Jeffrey, Curran, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Johnson, Alice Owens, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Johnson, Ronald, 1964-1975 (Box 4)
  - Jones, Joel, undated (Box 4)
  - Jones, Leroi (Amiri Baraka), 1963 (Box 4)
  - Joris, Pierre and Paige Mitchell, 1977 (Box 4)
  - "K" General, 1965-2007; (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Kallweit, Richard, 1974 (Box 4)
    Richard Kallweit served as co-editor of Criss Cross and co-founder of Drop City.
  - Kamei, Marlene, 1980 (Box 4)
  - Kandel, Lenore, 1969 (Box 4)
    Includes correspondence and papers related to Kandel's "Love Lust" poem.
  - Katzman, Al, undated (Box 4)
  - Keller, Gene, 1991 (Box 4)
    Gene Keller was an El Paso musician.
  - Keller, Michael, undated (Box 4)
  - Kelly, Douglas (Univ. of Wisconsin Professor Emeritus), 1956-1959 (Box 4)
  - Kelly, Robert, 1964-1965; (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Kennedy, John L., 1998 (Box 4)
    John L. Kennedy was a writer of pornography and Larry Goodell's neighbor.
  - Kenny, Maurice, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Knoll, John, 1983-1989 (Box 4)
  - Koller, James (Coyote), 1987 (Box 4)
  - Kornblum, Alland, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Kraft, Jim, 1980 (Box 4)
  - Kulp-Hill, Kathleen, 1962-2016; (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Kunz, Peter, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Kushner, Steven, undated (Box 4)
    Steven Kushner is also known as "Kush" and is affiliated with Cloud House, an archive of contemporary American poetry.
  - Kyger, Joanne, 1991-1995 (Box 4)
  - "L" General, 1964-1991; (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Lake, Larry, 1983 (Box 4)
    Larry Lake was a Denver-based poet.
  - Lancombe, Samuel, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Lawless, Gary, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Levering, Donald, 1984-1990 (Box 4)
    Donald Levering is a Santa Fe-based poet.
  - Lewis, Harry, undated (Box 4)
  - Lloyd, Robert, 1970-1984; (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Loewinsohn, Rob, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Lowell, Jim, 1964-1966; (4 folders) (Box 4)
    Includes correspondence and Asphodel Books catalogs.
  - Lowenfels, Walter, 1965 (Box 4)
  - Lucero-Giaccardo, Felice, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Luschei, Glenna, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Luster, Helen, 1963-1964 (Box 4)
  - "M" General, 1964-1997; (3 folders) (Box 5)
  - Mackie, J., 1987 (Box 5)
  - Mackintosh, Graham, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Macleod, Norman, 1984-1989; (3 folders) (Box 5)
  - Maher, Janet, 1984-1989 (Box 5)
  - Malanga, Gerard, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Malone, Marvin (Wormwood Review), undated (Box 5)
  - Mariah, Paul (Manroot), 1974 (Box 5)
  - Martin, John (Black Sparrow Press), 1978 (Box 5)
  - Masters, Greg, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Mattingly, George, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Mayfield, Carl M., 1974-2010 (Box 5)
  - McAleer, J. Neil, 1965 (Box 5)
  - McClure, Michael, 1977 (Box 5)
  - McCook, Kendall, 1984-2010; (2 folders) (Box 5)
    Kendall Cook, a close friend of Larry Goodell, worked as promoter for poet Kell Robertson. This file includes correspondence and writings.
  - McGaw, Bruce, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Meltzer, David, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Merrill, Jo, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Merrill, Susan, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Micheline, Jack, 1972 (Box 5)
  - Mitchell, Emerson Blackhorse Barney, undated (Box 5)
  - Mock, Richard, 1994 (Box 5)
    Includes correspondence and Mock's writing contribution to the "If It Doesn't Fit, Force It" magazine.
  - Moratt, Barbara, 1965-1966 (Box 5)
  - Moore, Todd, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Moritz, John (Tansy Press), 1976 (Box 5)
  - Morris, Harry O., 1979 (Box 5)
  - Morris, James Ryan, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Morris, Richard (Cosmep), 1974 (Box 5)
  - Moser, Norman, 1973 (Box 5)
  - Moulder, John, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Mowat, Suzanne, 1966-1967 (Box 5)
  - Murphy, Merilene (Telepoetics), 1991-1994; (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Myles, Eileen, 1991-2000; (2 folders) (Box 5)
    Includes correspondence, writings, and materials related to the "Eileen Myles for President '92" campaign.
  - "N" General, 1992-2013 (Box 5)
  - Nelson, Neil, 1973 (Box 5)
  - Nickell, Joe, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Nicolai, Scott, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Nelson, Curt, 1971 (Box 5)
  - New Mexico Poetry Renaissance (Red Crane Books), 1994 (Box 5)
  - New American Poetry Circuit, 1966-1971 (Box 5)
  - Noyes, Stanley, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Numerology (Larry Goodell personal charts), undated (Box 5)
  - Nye, Chris, undated (Box 5)
  - "O" General, undated (Box 5)
  - Oandasan, William, 1974 (Box 5)
    Oandasan was a Native American poet who wrote "Died Young".
  - Oliveros, Pauline, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Olson, Charles, 1964-1994 (Box 5)
  - Ortiz, Simon, undated (Box 5)
  - Orzen, Bill, undated (Box 5)
  - Owen, Maureen, 1980-1982 (Box 5)
  - "P" General, 1972-2010 (Box 5)
  - Pacheco, Henry L., 1974 (Box 5)
  - Palmer, Michael (George), 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Pearlman, Bill, 1971-2003; (9 folders) (Box 5)
    Includes correspondence and drafts for "Summer Harvest" and "Flareup of Twosomes".
  - Peckinpah, Deneen, 1968 (Box 5)
    Deneen Peckinpah is daughter of filmmaker Sam Peckinpah.
  - Peterson, Robert, 1974-2013 (Box 5)
  - Peyster, Steven (Verde Valley School, Sedona, AZ), 1976 (Box 5)
  - Phelan, Pat (Orogrande), 1979 (Box 5)
  - Philpott, Wayne, undated (Box 5)
  - Plymell, Charles, 1975-1978 (Box 5)
  - Poetry Project, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Potts, Charles, 1964-1998; (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Powell, Clarence Alva, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Price, Barrett, 1963-1977 (Box 5)
  - Prynne, J. H., 1966 (Box 5)
  - Puerto Del Sol Magazine (David Apodaca and Peter Kunz), 1971-1975 (Box 5)
  - Purcell, Pete and Fran, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Quin, Ann, 1965-1971; (7 folders) (Box 6)
  - Quintana, Leroy, 1971-1981 (Box 6)
  - "R" General, 1969-2005; (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Rabbit, Peter (nee Peter Douthit), 1982-2002 (Box 6)
  - Raetze, Gina, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Rage, Henry, 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Randall, Margaret, 1964-2006; (4 folders) (Box 6)
    Includes correspondence and "So Many Rooms Has a House But One Roof" draft.
  - Raworth, Tom, 1986-1990 (Box 6)
  - Reyes, Carlos, 1964-1968 (Box 6)
  - Rice, Meredith (artist), 1976 (Box 6)
  - Ricci, Roy, 1986-2010 (Box 6)
  - Rieke, Zack and Gail, 1974-1980 (Box 6)
  - Rio Grande Writers Association, 1978-1991; (3 folders) (Box 6)
    Includes clippings, schedules, and buisness notes related to "Downtown Saturday Night" events.
  - Robertson, Kell, 1966-1975; (5 folders) (Box 6)
  - Rodefer, Stephen, 1974-1990; (3 folders) (Box 6)
  - Rodgers, Ron, 1975 (Box 6)
  - Romero, Janet Stein and Nicasio, 1974-2008 (Box 6)
  - Romero, Leo, 1985-1991; (2 folders) (Box 6)
    Includes correspondence and a book review written by Larry Goodell.
  - Romero, Levi, 1991-2015 (Box 6)
  - Rosenblum, Martin J. (Albatross Press), 1971 (Box 6)
  - Roth, Moira, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Rothenberg, Jerome, 1964-1991 (Box 6)
  - Rothfork, John, 1980-1981 (Box 6)
  - "S" General, 1959-2008; (3 folders) (Box 6)
    Includes correspondence and submitted writings.
  - Sagel, Jim, 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Sanchez, Ricardo, 1991-1993 (Box 6)
  - Sanders, Ted, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Sanders, Jo, 1971 (Box 6)
  - Saroyan, Aram (Lines), 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Saville, Ken, 1974-1984; (2 folders) (Box 6)
    Includes correspondence and a number of Transient Press unsent postcards, many of which are signed.
  - Schroeder, Rick and Shiri, 1964 (Box 6)
    Includes correspondence and draft writings by Larry Goodell.
  - Schwerner, Armand, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Scott, Winfield Townley, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Scrivener, Michael, 1967 (Box 6)
  - Seder, Dave, undated (Box 6)
  - Seegar, Goyo Sabbath, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Sewards, Miki, undated (Box 6)
  - Shepherd, Jeff, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Sherman, Jory, undated (Box 6)
  - Shultis, Chris, 1989-2005 (Box 6)
  - Skinner, Betty, 1997-2001 (Box 6)
  - Silko, Leslie, undated (Box 6)
  - Sinclair, John and Leni and Robine Eichele, 1965-1967; (2 folders) (Box 6)
    Includes correspondence and materials related to the Detroit Artists' Workshop.
  - Smith, Bill, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Smith, Nick, undated (Box 6)
  - Smith, Phil, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Snow, Tony/Anthony Nieve, undated (Box 6)
  - Snyder, Gary, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Somoza, Joseph, 1974-1994; (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Sonneman, Eve, 1972-1974 (Box 7)
  - Sorestad, Glen, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Sorrels, Rosalie, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Southwestern Discoveries Magazine, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Spencer, Sam, undated (Box 7)
  - Spicer, Ron, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Srinivasan, R., 1965-2007 (Box 7)
  - Stageberg, Mia Kirsi, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Stavros, undated (Box 7)
  - Stein, Chuck, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Stetson, Catherine, 1965-1974 (Box 7)
  - Stone, Justin, 1972 (Box 7)
  - Streeter, Dante, 1960 (Box 7)
  - Stuart, Joseph and Signe Nelson, 1964-1965 (Box 7)
  - Sublette, Ned, 1976-1988; (2 folders) (Box 7)
    Includes correspondence and materials related to Ned Sublette's collaboration with Larry Goodell on a radio performance project.
  - Sundstrom, Bill and Darilyn, 1969 (Box 7)
  - SWPC (Southwest Poets Conference), 1973 (Box 7)
  - Sze, Arthur, 1978-1983 (Box 7)
  - "T" General, 1969-1990 (Box 7)
  - Taggart, John, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Tammer, David (Symptom), 1965-1968 (Box 7)
  - Tarasque, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Tarn, Nathaniel and Janet Rodney, 1983-2010; (3 folders) (Box 7)
  - Tart, Indrek, 1991-1992 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Chuck, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Teach, Gary, 1954-1962; (4 folders) (Box 7)
  - Tedlock, Dennis, 1982; (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Thayler, Carl, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Thompson, Richard, undated (Box 7)
  - Thompson, Tracy, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Thurmond, Clay, 1979-1982 (Box 7)
  - Tice, Arden, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Tobia, Blaise and Virginia Maksymowicz, 1981-1983 (Box 7)
  - Tick Lock (Joe Perrachio), 2002 (Box 7)
  - Tritica, John, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Tucker, Greg, 1989 (Box 7)
  - "V" General, 1965-2005 (Box 7)
  - Ubik Sound, 2005 (Box 7)
  - Vermont, Charlie and Anne, undated (Box 7)
  - The Vortex Theatre (Albuquerque), 1985 (Box 7)
  - Wagner, Linda, 1963 (Box 7)
  - Wagnon, Drew (Wild Dog), 1964 (Box 7)
  - Wah, Fred and Pauline, 1967-1984 (Box 7)
  - Wakowski, Diane, 1964-1965 (Box 7)
  - Walbridge, Ralph, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Waldman, Anne, 1986 (Box 7)
  - Weishus, Joel, undated (Box 7)
  - Witherup, Bill, 1971-1986 (Box 7)
  - Ward, Frederick, undated; (3 folders) (Box 7)
  - Walsh, Lewis, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Watson, Richard, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Webb, John and Gypsy Lou, 1965 (Box 7)
    Includes correspondence and ephemera related to Louson Press.
  - Weber, Mark, 1976-1996; (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Weil, James (Elizabeth Press), 1964 (Box 7)
  - Weinstein, Norman, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Whalen, Philip, 1963-1967 (Box 7)
  - Wiater, Michael, undated (Box 7)
  - Wilk, David, 1974 (Box 8)
  - Williams, Dennis, undated (Box 8)
  - WIlliams, Jonathan--incl. LG to Williams, 1964-1984; (2 folders) (Box 8)
    Includes correspondence and materials related to the Jargon Society.
  - Wilson, Keith, 1964-2008; (7 folders) (Box 8)
    Includes correspondence, materials related to the Jargon Society, and writing drafts of "Poems of Graphic Intent", "Stone Roses...", and "American Collage".
  - Winans, A. D., undated (Box 8)
  - Winson, Robert (Sycamore) and Miriam Sagan, 1985-1990 (Box 8)
  - Woodle, Mary, 1981-1983 (Box 8)
  - The Writer's Page, 1979-1980 (Box 8)
  - Young, Geoff and Laura Chester, 1975-2003 (Box 8)
  - Zukofsky, Louis, 1965 (Box 8)